— JACOB GINIEWSKI .—

CONTACT



321-614-1899



iakeginiewski@gmail.com

PROFILE

My name is Jacob Giniewski, and I am 18 years old. Though I have had little previous work experience, I have been an involved member of my community and have taken part in various volunteer and nonprofit organizations. I believe myself to be a talented communicator and driven worker and am prepared to do my best to do a job right. I am also very technologically literate, having earned multiple software certifications and taught myself how to build and repair PCs. I am a fast learner and should be able to get the hang of most jobs quickly.

SKILLS

- **CERTIFIED IN MICROSOFT** WORD, EXCEL, AND **POWERPOINT**
- STRONG LEADERSHIP AND **PLANNING SKILLS**
- SKILLED WITH ADOBE **PHOTOSHOP**
- **SOME PROGRAMMING** KNOWLEDGE IN JAVA, PYTHON, AND C

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

Earned 2019

Graduated having taken 9 AP classes and 2 college classes

EXPERIENCE

Boy Scouts of America (Troop 309)

2011-2019

I am currently working on earning the rank of Eagle Scout. In Boy Scouts, I have held multiple terms as Senior Patrol Leader and Patrol Leader. I have put in hundreds of hours volunteering for the community and have completed my Eagle Scout project. My time with the Boy Scouts has given me years of experience in leadership and communication, as well as a drive to work hard and succeed in my endeavors.

FIRST Robotics Competition (Team 386)

2015-2019

I was a member of FIRST Robotics Team 386 Voltage. I worked in the team's business group, and primarily handled the team's graphic design needs. In addition to my graphical work, I helped to communicate with sponsors, build our community presence, and write our team's business plan. Working with Team Voltage has helped me to excel in working with small groups and presenting my ideas effectively.

Codecraft Lab

2013-2017

I have put in over a hundred hours volunteering for Codecraft Lab, a nonprofit organization dedicated to teaching children how to code. My volunteer work was mostly helping to run summer camps, where I assisted kids ages 7-12 who were learning how to use primarily Scratch, Python, and Kodu game lab. I also administrated the camp's game server, a role which required me to settle disputes almost daily. My time at Codecraft helped me to gain vast amounts of patience and made me a much more responsible person than I was when I started.

Wartsila

July 2019

In July of 2019, I was hired to do a year's worth of document organization at a Wartsila office in Melbourne, Florida. With the help of a coworker, the project was completed in a matter of days. During that time, I had to label and alphabetize hundreds of sales invoices. My manager was very satisfied with my work upon completion.
•